{
  "decks": [
    {
      "name": "Cheepis Quiz",
      "description": "Only true Cheepi can pass this quiz!!",
      "id": 4
    }
  ],
  "cards": [
    {
      "front": "An identifier word for \"best cat\".",
      "back": "Cheepis [CHEEP-iss] noun",
      "id": 7,
      "deckId": 4
    },
    {
      "front": "The full name of fat hamster.",
      "back": "Professor Moon Racer Rocket Man Winter Melon",
      "id": 8,
      "deckId": 4
    },
    {
      "front": "The combination of a rodent psychic and a strong tree-like man.",
      "back": "Baby Gremlin or Lil' Boy!!!",
      "id": 9,
      "deckId": 4
    },
    {
      "front": "M",
      "back": "I",
      "deckId": 4,
      "id": 10
    },
    {
      "front": "S",
      "back": "T",
      "deckId": 4,
      "id": 11
    },
    {
      "front": "E",
      "back": "R",
      "deckId": 4,
      "id": 12
    },
    {
      "front": "Mister mister mister!!!",
      "back": "Oh",
      "deckId": 4,
      "id": 13
    },
    {
      "front": "Mister mister!!!!",
      "back": "Ohhhh",
      "deckId": 4,
      "id": 14
    },
    {
      "front": "MISTER!!",
      "back": "OHHHHH!!",
      "deckId": 4,
      "id": 15
    },
    {
      "front": "This treat is either a vegetable or a feline attractant.",
      "back": "Celery/Catnip",
      "deckId": 4,
      "id": 16
    },
    {
      "front": "Name one of two of my favorite League of Legend skins.",
      "back": "Acceptable answers: Team Spirit Anivia or Molten Rammus",
      "deckId": 4,
      "id": 17
    },
    {
      "front": "The drug that one Cheepis is recovering from.",
      "back": "T*********ng M*rs",
      "deckId": 4,
      "id": 18
    },
    {
      "front": "Name every Mister currently in this room.",
      "back": "Mister, Mister Cat, Mister Moon, Mister Nugget, Mister Nibbis, Mister Squirrel",
      "deckId": 4,
      "id": 19
    },
    {
      "front": "This is how much Cheepis love the Cheepi have for each other.",
      "back": "Infinite",
      "deckId": 4,
      "id": 20
    },
    {
      "front": "The Cheepis building we will head to after this question is done.",
      "back": "Catnip 0_0",
      "deckId": 4,
      "id": 21
    }
  ]
}